<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-10-24T18:33:36+05:45</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Durga Pokharel</title><subtitle>A girl pursuing MSc. Mathematics on CDM TU.  </subtitle><author><name>Durga Pokharel</name></author><entry><title type="html">The Power of ‘What if?’</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/09/19/the-power-of-what-if/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Power of 'What if?'" /><published>2020-09-19T01:29:17+05:45</published><updated>2020-09-19T01:29:17+05:45</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/09/19/the-power-of-what-if</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/09/19/the-power-of-what-if/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What if I did this? What if I couldn’t do this?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Durga Pokharel</name></author><category term="thoughts" /><category term="journal" /><summary type="html">Introduction What if I did this? What if I couldn’t do this?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Blogging Journey</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/09/19/my-blogging-journey/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Blogging Journey" /><published>2020-09-19T01:29:17+05:45</published><updated>2020-09-19T01:29:17+05:45</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/09/19/my-blogging-journey</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/09/19/my-blogging-journey/">&lt;h2 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was teaching secondary level students on 2019 and I was learning lots of things during that 1 year. It was really an amazing experience that I could share lots of thing and at the same time I learned the best practices that can be done my teachers to help students on their studies. And one of them is blogging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;how-am-i-here&quot;&gt;How am I here?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It really is hard for me to start blogging and all these tech stuffs were totally new to me but not until we try to learn it. So on 2019, I was trying to learn Python programming language, I wrote my first ever class on programming language on 2019. I was interested on Application of Mathematics on Machine Learning but due to personal problems, I couldn’t learn these much. Then while doing my MSc, I learned Latex, of course it is not a programming language. Then one of my friend suggested me to do blogging about the assignments and courseworks on our MSc degree. It was totally tough start for me not because I was new to this world but I am on village far from city and good Internet Connection. Due to COVID-19, I am on my village learning blogging and taking online classes using cellular data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;okay-but-how-am-i-doing-it&quot;&gt;Okay but how am I doing it?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started with GitHub account and then ended with this platform. There are lot to learn and I am just a beginner on this field. But writing about my steps, there are few:-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Made GitHub account and learned about Git (still learning).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Made a simple Jekyll site using default theme (i.e Minima) (I didn’t knew what is theme until I tried this).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Heard about Minimal Mistakes, then tried it and glad to find this soon.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Configured Google Analytics and Search Consoles.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-can-i-write-about&quot;&gt;What can I write about?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am planning on writing about simple mathematics problems for Nepali students and target is Mathematics students. But if I got bored, I can write about some journal also.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Durga Pokharel</name></author><category term="thoughts" /><category term="journal" /><summary type="html">Introduction I was teaching secondary level students on 2019 and I was learning lots of things during that 1 year. It was really an amazing experience that I could share lots of thing and at the same time I learned the best practices that can be done my teachers to help students on their studies. And one of them is blogging.</summary></entry></feed>